+44 7375 658278

ZIYAD PATEL

PROFILE

Passionate and confident Frontend Developer with skills in JS, HTML, CSS, React, Next.JS, SQL

Always trying to gain new knowledge. Aiming to be a full stack, experienced developer working on improving software and websites, whilst innovating on and enhancing UX.

Skills

- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Project Management

- UI/UX Design
- Innovative
- Analytical

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Customer Care Advisor at Mountain Warehouse

June 2021 – Present

- Conducted training sessions for new customer care representatives
- Resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and professional manner, resulting in improving our first contact resolutions to +90%
- Monitored customer feedback and responded to customer inquiries on social media
- Identified and addressed customer service issues, resulting in a higher customer satisfaction scores and improved processes for staff.

Ziyad Patel +44 7375 658278

Factory Worker at Leicester Interiors

July 2020 — May 2021

- Assembled products, meeting production targets and deadlines
- Fitted products into homes, ensuring customers were happy with the outcome
- Performed quality control checks, ensuring products met established standards
- Improved production line output by around 25% by streamlining workflow processes
- Performed data entry and updated production reports
- Greeted guests in a friendly, professional manner and provided prompt, efficient service

COURSES

UX Design at Google, Coursera

June 2022 — September 2022

EDUCATION

BSc (Hons) Computing & IT and Business, The Open University Law 2022 - Present

Studying full-time, alongside working part-time. Using the knowledge gained to improve my understanding of business and the quality of my programming work.

BSc (Hons) Psychology & Cognitive Neuroscience, **University of Leicester**

Completed first year, wanted to move into a different industry.

A-Level, Wyggeston & Queen Elizabeth I College, Leicester September 2019 – June 2021

Psychology: B, English language: B, Biology: C

GCSE, Crown Hills Community College, Leicester

September 2014 - May 2019

English: 7, Maths: 7, Science: 7, History: 8, Drama: 9, IT: 8, Citizenship: 7